I see Xuan Kingdom's flag
Я видел знамя Сюаньго
I see Xuan Kingdom's military flag
Я видел военное знамя Сюаньго
The royal army is going north
Царское войско идёт на север
Stop wailing
Что орёшь как на похоронах
Can you even read?
Ты вообще читать умеешь
I only know
Я узнал
My father drew it for me before he died
Мой отец нарисовал его перед смертью
That really is Xuan Kingdom's military flag
Это точно знамя Сюаньго
I see so many soldiers
Я видел многомного солдат
If you don't believe me, come and see
Не верите пойдёмте со мной посмотрите
Really
Правда
Come on, come on
Пошли пошли
Hurry up
Быстрее
Your Highness
Ваше Высочество
That little thief we chased earlier
Тот воришка за которым мы гнались
Has brought a group of people over
привёл с собой целую толпу
It really is Xuan Kingdom's military flag
Действительно знамя Сюаньго
It's true
Это правда
We respectfully welcome the royal army going north
С почтением приветствуем царское войско идущее на север
Sheathe your swords
Убрать мечи
Dismount
Слезть с коней
All rise
Вставайте все
Hearing the royal army is going north
Услышали что царское войско идёт на север
Passing through our village
и пройдёт через нашу деревню
We
мы
Gathered some grain
собрали немного зерна
Everyone, share it
Пусть все возьмут понемногу
Sir
Господин
The village
Нашу деревню
Has been stripped bare by the Wutu
племена Уну разграбили дочиста
This
Это
Please don't look down on it
Вы только не откажитесь